so get ready community oh by the way so
that's how mafia guys get rich they gave
some money into their nephew ten years
ago they did one nice thing then they
killed 20 people but the gift of a few
some money to their nephew made them
rich and it will always go away will
always collapse okay all right
mafia guys wealthiest bird poop seeds
accident
so please come to your breath you can
check in with the llama in your heart
you don't have to do the full
preliminaries every session you can do
it once in the morning and then in the
following sessions on the same day you
can just check in with your llama
sitting in a grain of crisps a grain of
sugar in your heart like a clear crystal
globe
and bring your mind to the center to
your breath let go of the outside world
like all the things happening everywhere
in your life these three days are your
days let go of all the other things
you're doing and you will find that you
do them better afterwards come to your
breath
then I'd like you to think about some
pretty serious mistakes you've made in
your life maybe before you knew about
Karma and those are kind of like time
bombs therapist those seeds didn't come
back to us yet many of them and some of
those actions were pretty serious you
know I was involved in an abortion I can
think of that kind of when I was in
college so I can think of time bombs
waiting for me you know some very heavy
negative Karma's are waiting inside of
me and at some point they will blow up
and I now get some very serious problems
so this meditation is the first part is
a little bit difficult we have to try to
think of people that we really hurt or
mistakes like that that we made mostly
that so we'll take a few minutes try to
think of one or two grand mistakes
you've made in your life
and
didn't think about the few things you're
doing nowadays where you are taking good
refuge you are using the four steps you
are trying to make things happen by
helping other people it doesn't have to
be a big thing maybe you are helping a
friend with a relationship problem or
maybe you're helping someone financially
but you are taking baby steps to deal
with problems and to reach goals by
serving someone else so think of two or
three things you're doing which are
using seeds which are serving others to
reach your goals and that's taking
refuge think of that times you're taking
refuge
and
the third and last part of this
meditation is to just spend a few
minutes appreciating that the baby steps
you are taking to solve problems or
reach goals by serving others planting
seeds actually damage the old godsey's
so understanding where things come from
reaching goals by planting seeds by
serving other people helping them reach
their goals the power of those baby
steps small baby steps is very very
powerful and Lomb rim says it will block
or destroy even very old powerful bad
seeds so try to draw a mental connection
between the small good things you're
doing now with understanding seeds
taking refuge and draw a line in your
mind back to those big mistakes you made
many years ago in my case 45 years ago
and appreciate that that new way of life
is damaging and disabling the old bad
seeds and you are again you are
protecting yourself from those time bugs
drive that mine and you might make that
connection
and
then watch 3d 3dd exhales don't move
here don't open your eyes check in with
your lumber in your heart and then open
your eyes take a stretch